<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awesome Omniverse</title>
    <description>This is my website blog about web technologies like Javascript, HTML5, CSS and also about entertainment content of my own interest, so keep it cool and stay awesome!
</description>
    <link>http://jcortes.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jcortes.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 11:49:25 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 11:49:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cambly Article N01</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This post is related to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.cambly.com/2015/05/14/why-google-failed-according-to-google-insiders&quot;&gt;cambly post&lt;/a&gt; about why google plus failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;brief-summary&quot;&gt;Brief Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google has been trying to make Google Plus more popular than Facebook or Twitter, but
it did not work because Google Plus was made for companies and not for people.
However a lot of people are still using it because it is the way to easily loggin to all Google
applications online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-is-google-changing-its-strategy-for-google&quot;&gt;Why is Google changing its strategy for Google+?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because users do not feel like they are using a social network or something like Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;was-google-successful-at-getting-people-to-talk-about-google&quot;&gt;Was Google successful at getting people to talk about Google+?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, They were not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;google-was-designed-to-solve-the-companys-own-problems&quot;&gt;Google+ was designed to solve the company’s own problems&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think this was the big problem with Google Plus, just because they did not think about 
people around the world. Maybe because of that Facebook and Twitter
for example have more success, they had people’s requirements in mind and not their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-has-been-the-most-successful-parts-of-google&quot;&gt;What has been the most successful parts of Google+&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photo Application and Video Streaming&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-conclusion&quot;&gt;My Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe Google will try to find a way to serve as a Photo Managing and Streaming Video
platform in the future, but I might be wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 08:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://jcortes.github.io/cambly/2015/05/20/cambly-article01.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jcortes.github.io/cambly/2015/05/20/cambly-article01.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cambly</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
